Information Studies, Department of; Records ua671
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Web Archives, 2011 February 2-2016 September 18; 6; 313 captures
  Surface-level crawling of www.albany.edu is performed daily which should includes most top-level webpages. Separate targeted crawls of every albany.edu subdomain are performed monthly to attempt to gather all content. This includes: www.albany.edu, www.rna.albany.edu, www.ctg.albany.edu, www.ualbanysports.com, www.albany.edu/rockefeller, www.albany.edu/cela, www.albany.edu/asrc, m.albany.edu, library.albany.edu, events.albany.edu, cstar.cestm.albany.edu, csda.albany.edu, and alumni.albany.edu
  Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
  Web Archives
  - http://www.albany.edu/informationstudies/ - University Archives collection, 2013 May 8-2016 September 18 (Web-archive 1)
  - WARC file for http://www.albany.edu/informationstudies/, (please see https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Web_ARChive for more details), 2013 May 8-2016 September 18 (Warc 1)
    WARC files are very large and difficult to work with. Your request may take time to process, and we may be unable to deliver your request remotely. Please consult an archivist if you are interested in researching with web archives.
  - http://www.albany.edu/informationstudies/ - Internet Archive collection, 2011 February 2-2016 September 18 (Web-archive 2)